从单个的任务的执行上来讲呢
In terms of execution of a single task?
相对而言
relatively speaking
我觉得Claude Code体验会更加的平滑一些
I think the Claude Code experience will be smoother
对于项目的理解会更好一些
Understand the project better
对于项目的配置执行呢
What about project configuration execution?
也更平滑
Also smoother
而Codex在整个项目的理解和运行上
And Codex is very important in understanding and running the entire project.
似乎在某些方面
It seems that in some ways
还会显得有些磕磕绊绊
It will also look a little stumbling.
特别是在后续
Especially in the follow-up
对于这个Swift项目的执行上
For the execution of this Swift project
花了蛮多时间去理解梳理
It took a lot of time to understand and sort out
来最终帮我将这个应用程序启动起来
Come finally help me get this app up and running
当然了这也是我在这个特定的应用
Of course that's what I'm doing in this particular application
特定的任务执行上的一个直观的感觉
An intuitive feel for specific task execution
那么大家在日常的开发中
So in daily development, everyone
是否已经开始使用这些模型
Have you started using these models?
大家在使用中的体验怎么样呢
How is your experience in using it?
欢迎在评论区给我留言
Welcome to leave me a message in the comment area
那今天的分享就先到这里
So today’s sharing will start here.
感谢大家收看我们下次视频分享
Thank you everyone for watching our next video sharing
再见同学们拜拜
Goodbye, classmates.